multibit.org 2019-02-24

# Legal - Privacy Policy | MultiBit

### Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to multibit.org and the MultiBit software, and governs data collection and usage. The MultiBit website contains information and downloads for the MultiBit software. By using the MultiBit website and software, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

#### Collection of your Personal Information

MultiBit may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by MultiBit. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the MultiBit website.

MultiBit encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from MultiBit so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. MultiBit is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the MultiBit website.

#### Information Gathered by the Software

Older versions of MultiBit contained the BRIT service, which allowed for the collection of fees in order to support development. As of version v0.3.0, BRIT service was removed and now no information is gathered by the software.

During wallet creation in older versions of MultiBit, a unique irreversible identifier was created and sent to our site. This was stored and used as follows:

  * to provide a timestamp lookup facility to assist with faster synchronization
  * to ensure that the same fee payment addresses were supplied for the same wallet words

The unique identifier:

  *  **did not** allow us reverse engineer wallet words or any other wallet information
  *  **did not** allow us to spend or recover bitcoins
  *  **did not** allow us to identify you as an individual (no IP address is stored for example)
  *  **did not** allow us to track you

#### Use of your Personal Information

MultiBit collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

MultiBit may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from MultiBit and its affiliates. MultiBit may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

MultiBit does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

MultiBit may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to MultiBit, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

MultiBit may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within MultiBit, in order to determine what MultiBit services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within MultiBit to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

#### Use of Cookies

The MultiBit website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize MultiBit pages, or register with MultiBit site or services, a cookie helps MultiBit to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same MultiBit website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the MultiBit features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the MultiBit services or websites you visit.

#### Security of your Personal Information

MultiBit secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

#### Children Under Thirteen

MultiBit does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

#### Changes to this Statement

MultiBit will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. MultiBit encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how MultiBit is protecting your information.

#### Contact Information

MultiBit welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that MultiBit has not adhered to this Statement, please contact MultiBit at:

KeepKey, LLC.  
570 Kirkland Way  
Kirkland, Washington 98033

Email Address:  
support@multibit.org

Telephone number:  
1-855-463-8550

Effective as of June 01, 2016
